Guide to the Argus Archives Records
Argus Archives Records
- Related Items, 1980-2003; 14.8 linear feet
  - Humane Education Curriculum Extras, 1992-1993 (Box 10.003, Folder 1)
  - Humane Education Curriculum, Grades 5-6, 1990 (Box 10.003, Folder 2)
  - Humane Education Curriculum, Grades 1-6 (Folder 1 of 2), 1990 (Box 10.003, Folder 3)
  - Humane Education Curriculum, Grades 1-6 (Folder 2 of 2), 1990 (Box 10.003, Folder 4)
  - Humane Education Curriculum, Grades 3-4, 1990 (Box 10.003, Folder 5)
  - Humane Education Curriculum, Dog & Cat Overpopulation: 101 A Teaching Unit for 3rd-5th Grades, circa, 1990 (Box 10.003, Folder 6)
  - Humane Education Curriculum, Grades K-2, 1988 (Box 10.003, Folder 7)
  - Legislative materials, 1972 (Box 10.004, Folder 1)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 1 of 11), 1990-1997 (Box 10.004, Folder 2)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 2 of 11), 1990-1997 (Box 10.004, Folder 3)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 3 of 11), 1992-1994 (Box 10.004, Folder 4)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 4 of 11), 1993-1995 (Box 10.004, Folder 5)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 5 of 11), 1993-1997 (Box 10.004, Folder 6)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 6 of 11), 1994 (Box 10-004, Folder 6)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 7 of 11), 1994 (Box 10-005, Folder 1)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 8 of 11), 1994 (Box 10-005, Folder 2)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 9 of 11), 1994 (Box 10-005, Folder 3)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 10 of 11), 1994-1996 (Box 10-005, Folder 4)
  - Magazine Periodicals (Folder 11 of 11), 1996-1998 (Box 10-005, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Pamphlets (Folder 1 of 8)), circa 1990 (Box 10.006, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Pamphlets (Folder 2 of 8), circa 1990 (Box 10.006, Folder 2)
  - Marketing Pamphlets (Folder 3 of 8), circa 1990 (Box 10.006, Folder 3)
  - Marketing Pamphlets (Folder 4 of 8), circa 1990 (Box 10.006, Folder 4)
  - Marketing Pamphlets (Folder 5 of 8), circa 1990 (Box 10.006, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Pamphlets (Folder 6 of 8), 1994-1995 (Box 10.006, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Pamphlets (Folder 7 of 8), 1994-1995 (Box 10.007, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Pamphlets (Folder 8 of 8), 1994-1995 (Box 10.007, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters (Folder 1 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.007, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters (Folder 2 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.007, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters (Folder 3 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.007, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters (Folder 4 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.008, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters (Folder 5 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.008, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters (Folder 6 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.008, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Folder 7 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.008, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters (Folder 8 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.008, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters (Folder 9 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.009, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters (Folder 10 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.009, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters (Folder 11 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.009, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Folder 12 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.009, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters (Folder 13 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10.009, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters (Folder 14 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-010, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters (Folder 15 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-010, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters (Folder 16 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-010, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Folder 17 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-010, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters (Folder 18 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-010, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters (Folder 19 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-011, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters (Folder 20 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-011, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters (Folder 21 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-011, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Folder 22 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-011, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters (Folder 23 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-011, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters (Folder 24 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-011, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters (Folder 25 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-012, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters (Folder 26 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-012, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters (Folder 27 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-012, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Folder 28 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-012, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters (Folder 29 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-012, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters (Folder 30 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-013, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters (Folder 31 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-013, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Folder 32 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-013, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Folder 33 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-013, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters (Folder 34 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-013, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters (Folder 35 of 35), 1990-1997 (Box 10-013, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 1 of 5), 1991-1994 (Box 10-014, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 2 of 5), 1992-1995 (Box 10-014, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 3 of 5), 1992-1997 (Box 10-014, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 4 of 5), 1978-1995 (Box 10-014, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 5 of 5), 1992-1995 (Box 10-014, Folder 5)
  - Publications (Folder 1 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-014, Folder 6)
  - Publications (Folder 2 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-015, Folder 1)
  - Publications (Folder 3 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-015, Folder 2)
  - Publications (Folder 4 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-015, Folder 3)
  - Publications (Folder 5 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-015, Folder 4)
  - Publications (Folder 6 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-015, Folder 5)
  - Publications (Folder 7 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-015, Folder 6)
  - Publications (Folder 8 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-016, Folder 1)
  - Publications (Folder 9 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-016, Folder 2)
  - Publications (Folder 10 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-016, Folder 3)
  - Publications (Folder 11 of 11), circa 1990-1997 (Box 10-016, Folder 4)
  - American Humane Association, 2000-2001 (Box 10-017, Folder 1)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): Pre-COP 10 Comments Submitted to US FWS, 1996-1997 (Box 10-017, Folder 2)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): COP 10 Conference in Harare, Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 10-017, Folder 3)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): COP 10 Documents, 1996-1997 (Box 10-017, Folder 4)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): Elephant Dowlisting Proposals (Folder 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 10-017, Folder 5)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): Elephoant Downlisting Proposals (Folder 2 of 2), 1997 (Box 10-017, Folder 6)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): E-mail List Excerpts, 1996-1998 (Box 10-017, Folder 7)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): NGO Positions and Recommendations, 1996-1997 (Box 10-017, Folder 8)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): Newspaper Articles (Folder 1 of 2), 1997 (Legalbox 10-018, Folder 1)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): Newspaper Articles (Folder 2 of 2), 1997 (Legalbox 10-018, Folder 2)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): Panel of experts' Review of Zimbabwe (Re: Downlisting), 1996 (Box 10-019, Folder 1)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): Pre-COP 10 Senate Letter, 1996-1997 (Box 10-019, Folder 2)
  - CITES (Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species): Press Information, 1996-1997 (Box 10-019, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 16), 1991 (Box 10-019, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 16), 1991 (Box 10-019, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 16), 1991-1992 (Box 10-019, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (Folder 4 of 16), 1991-1998 (Box 10-019, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (Folder 5 of 16), 1992-1996 (Box 10-019, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Folder 6 of 16), 1992-1997 (Box 10-019, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (Folder 7 of 16), 1992-2002 (Box 10-020, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 8 of 16), 1994-1996 (Box 10-020, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 9 of 16), 1994-1998 (Box 10-020, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 10 of 16), 1994-2000 (Box 10-020, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 11 of 16), 1994-2003 (Box 10-020, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 12 of 16), 1995 (Box 10-020, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (Folder 13 of 16), 1997-1998 (Box 10-021, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 14 of 16), 1997-2003 (Box 10-021, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 15 of 16), 2003 (Box 10-021, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 16 of 16), 2004 (Box 10-021, Folder 4)
  - Court Documents, 1995-2000 (Box 10-021, Folder 5)
  - Department of the Interior, Fish and Wildlife Service, Fiscal Year 1998 Appropriations (Box 10-021, Folder 6)
  - Department of the Interior: U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service (Folder 1 of 5), 1995-1997 (Box 10-021, Folder 7)
  - Department of the Interior: U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service (Folder 2 of 5), 1995-1997 (Box 10-021, Folder 8)
  - Department of the Interior: U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service (Folder 3 of 5), 1995-1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 1)
  - Department of the Interior: U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service (Folder 4 of 5), 1995-1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 2)
  - Department of the Interior: U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service (Folder 5 of 5), 1995-1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 3)
  - Disney's Animal Kingdom, 1998 (Box 10-022, Folder 4)
  - Dolphins: Background Information Facts and Figures Position Statements Research, 1996-1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 5)
  - Dolphins: Action Alerts from Pro-Dolphin Organizations, 1997-1998 (Box 10-022, Folder 6)
  - Dolphins: Correspondence - General, 1997-1998 (Box 10-022, Folder 7)
  - Dolphins: Correspondence - Legislators, 1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 8)
  - Dolphins: Fact Sheets from Anti-Dolphin Organizations, 1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 9)
  - Dolphins: Fact Sheets from Pro-Dolphin Organizations, 1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 10)
  - Dolphins: Fisheries, Wildlife and Oceans Subcommittee Hearing and H.R. 408, 1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 11)
  - Dolphins: Fisheries, Wildlife and Oceans Subcommittee. Markup of H.R. 408 (Box 10-022, Folder 12)
  - Dolphins: Rules Committee, Full Committee, Markup of H.R. 408, 1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 13)
  - Dolphins: Letters from Students, 1997 (Box 10-022, Folder 14)
  - Dolphins: Miscellaneous Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 10-023, Folder 1)
  - Dolphins: Oceans & Fisheries Subcommittee Hearing, 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 2)
  - Dolphins: Press Releases from Pro-Dolphin Organizations, 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 3)
  - Dolphins: Panama Declaration and La Jolla Agreement, 1980-1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 4)
  - Dolphins: Press Releases - Legislators, 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 5)
  - Dolphins: Opposition, 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 6)
  - Dolphins: Safe/Fair Trade Campaign, 1997-1998 (Box 10-023, Folder 7)
  - Dolphins: Student Rally (Barbara Boxer and Joe Biden, guest speakers), 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 8)
  - Humane Education Groups: Sahu Vaswani, 1999 (Box 10-023, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: African Elephant Conservation Act - Oversight Hearing, 1996 (Box 10-023, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Bill Summary and Status Information, 1997-1998 (Box 10-023, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Campbell Bill - California Endangered Species Act Waivers, 1998 (Box 10-023, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Comments Submitted by Endangered Species Act Committee, 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Congressional Green Sheets, 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Dolphins (Folder 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Dolphins (Folder 2 of 2), 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Draft Language, 1997 (Box 10-023, Folder 17)
  - Elephant Killings: Press Information (Folder 1 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 10-024, Folder 1)
  - Elephant Killings: Press Information (Folder 2 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 10-024, Folder 2)
  - Elephant Killings: Press Information (Folder 3 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 10-024, Folder 3)
  - Elephant Killings: Press Information (Folder 4 of 4), 1996-1998 (Box 10-024, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Endangered Species Act, Cheetah Downlisting Petition - Comment Letters, 1998 (Box 10-024, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Endangered Species Act, Newspaper Articles, 1997-1998 (Box 10-024, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Endangered Species Alerts, 1997 (Box 10-024, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Endangered Species Recovery Act (Folder 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 10-024, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Endangered Species Recovery Act (Folder 2 of 2), 1997 (Box 10-024, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Fisheries Subcommittee Hearing on H.R. 39 (the African Elephone Conservation Act of 1997) (Box 10-025, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Flood Control, Endangered Species Act Waivers, 1997 (Box 10-025, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: H.B. 1031; Live Elephant Prohibition, 1998 (Box 10-025, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: H.J. Res 59; Polar Bear Imports, 1999 (Box 10-025, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: H.R. 39, Young African Elephant Conservation Reauthorization, 1997 (Box 10-025, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: H.R. 453 and S.850; Downed Animal Protection Act, 1998 (Box 10-025, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: H.R. 741; H.R. 2863; and S. 153 (Folder 1 of 4), 1998 (Box 10-025, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: H.R. 741; H.R. 2863; and S. 153 (Folder 2 of 4), 1998 (Box 10-025, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: H.R. 741; H.R. 2863; and S. 153 (Folder 3 of 4), 1998 (Box 10-025, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: H.R. 741; H.R. 2863; and S. 153 (Folder 4 of 4), 1998 (Box 10-025, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: H.R. 1202, Capitve Exotic Animal Protection Act, 1997 (Box 10-025, Box 11)
  - Legislation: H.R. 752, Chenoweth Bill, 1980 (Box 10-026, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: H.R. 1787, Asian Elephants Act, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: H.R. 2291, Consfiscated Wildlife, 1998 (Box 10-026, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: H.R. 4717, Conservation and Reinvestment Act of 1998 (Oil Drilling Revenue Alternative to Teaming with Wildlife) (Box 10-026, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: House International Relations Committee, Subcommitee on Africa Economic Development of Africa, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Leghold Trap Legislation, 1998 (Box 10-026, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Public Law 105-42, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Public Law 105-96, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: S.462, Pet Ownership Provision, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: S.751 and H.R. 1719, The Sportsmen's Bill of Rights, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: S.1287, Asian Elephants Amendment, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: S.1489, The Outfitter Policy Act of 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: S.1693, Thomas' National Parks Bill, 1998 (Box 10-026, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Senate Committee on Environment and Public Works Full Committee Hearing, S.1287 and S.627, undated (Box 10-026, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Senate Environmental and Public Works Full Committee Hearing, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Subcommittee on Fisheries Conservation, Wildlife and Oceans, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Wilderness Act Hearings, 1997 (Box 10-026, Folder 17)
  - Marketing Pamphlets, circa, 1990 (Box 10-026, Folder 18)
  - Newsletters (Folder 1 of 2), 1991-1998 (Box 10-026, Folder 19)
  - Newsletters (Folder 2 of 2), 1991-1998 (Box 10-027, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 1 of 6), 1991-1998 (Box 10-027, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 2 of 6), 1993-1997 (Box 10-027, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 3 of 6), 1995-1999 (Box 10-027, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 4 of 6), 19981-1999 (Box 10-027, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 5 of 6), 2003 (Box 10-027, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Articles (Folder 6 of 6), 2003 (Box 10-027, Folder 7)
  - Organizations: "A" (Folder 1 of 4), 1991-2001 (Box 10-028, Folder 1)
  - Organizations: "A" (Folder 2 of 4), 1991-2001 (Box 10-028, Folder 2)
  - Organizations: "A" (Folder 3 of 4), 1991-2001 (Box 10-028, Folder 3)
  - Organizations: "A" (Folder 4 of 4), 1991-2001 (Box 10-028, Folder 4)
  - Organizations: "B-C", 1991-1992 (Box 10-028, Folder 5)
  - Organizations: "N" (Folder 1 of 2), 1991-1998 (Box 10-028, Folder 6)
  - Organizations: "N" (Folder 2 of 2), 1991-1998 (Box 10-028, Folder 7)
  - Organizations: "P" (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 10-029, Folder 1)
  - Organizations: "P" (Folder 2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 10-029, Folder 2)
  - Related Material (Folder 1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 10-029, Folder 3)
  - Related Material (Folder 2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 10-029, Folder 4)
  - USAID/Campfire: Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 10-029, Folder 5)
  - USAID/Campfire: Fiscal Year 98 Foreign Operations and Appropriations, 1997 (Box 10-029, Folder 6)
  - USAID/Campfire: Founding Sources Other than USAID, 1996-1998 (Box 10-029, Folder 7)
  - USAID/Campfire: House Appropriations Committee for Operations Subcommittee Hearing, 1997 (Box 10-029, Folder 8)
  - USAID/Campfire: Meeting Notes, 1996 (Box 10-030, Folder 1)
  - USAID/Campfire: Newspaper Articles, 1997 (Box 10-030, Folder 2)
  - USAID/Campfire: Safari Club International, 1997 (Box 10-030, Folder 3)
  - USAID/Campfire: Southern Africa Natural Resources Management, 1997 (Box 10-030, Folder 4)
  - USAID/Campfire: Zimbabwe, Africa Resources Trust, Campfire Connection, 1996-1998 (Box 10-030, Folder 5)
  - USAID/Campfire: Zimbabwe, Correspondence from Legislators, 1997 (Box 10-030, Folder 6)
  - USAID/Campfire: Zimbabwe, Letters to the Editor, 1996-1997 (Box 10-030, Folder 7)
  - USAID/Campfire: Zimbabwe Natuaral Resources Management Project, Midterm Evaluation, 1994 (Box 10-030, Folder 8)
  - USAID/Campfire: Zimbabwe, Natural Resources Management Project, Midterm Evaluation, Phase II (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 10-030, Folder 9)
  - USAID/Campfire: Zimbabwe, Natural Resources Management Project, Midterm Evaluation, Phase II (Folder 2 of 2), 1998 (Box 10-030, Folder 10)
  - USAID/Campfire: Zimbabwe, Park Rehabilitation and Conservation Project, Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 10-030, Folder 11)